guys we're gonna evaluate a piecewise
function so for
x equals seven which of these two is
true what's the top one because seven is
greater than four we are not going to
use this one this is telling us
that we're gonna use this function so f
of seven
is equal to and we're going to plug a 7
into the x
7 plus 2 and that equals 9. so the
answer to this
is 9. had this 7 been something
different like a 2 we would have ended
up using this
lower one this x squared because 2 is in
this domain i posted more of these
online if you want to try some more
there's a whole bunch of samples you can
watch a lot of them
there's a lot of samples you can try and
they all give the answers
it's 21 different ones you can try find
that page by going to andymath.com
on the homepage just type something like
evaluating piecewise functions and this
page will come up and that's the page i
just showed you please check it out i'd
love people to use it you're awesome
and i'll talk to you soon bye